Explore the world where everything is locked by default! Inspired by a popular Minecraft data pack Chunklock, this mod provides a unique challenge in which you have to get lots of bizarre and unique materials, just to... set foot on the new land? But listen, I tried making it less tedious and a lot more fun with the help of Surprises - random occurrences, which could happen when you unlock a chunk! But be careful, some do come with terrible consequences...

* Enjoy a varied and sometimes weird pool of items, required for unlocks!
* If you're feeling stuck, you can reroll any chunk you don't like!
* Obtain rerolls by defeating bosses or unlocking more chunks!
* Growing difficulty to make sure the progress doesn't feel boring!
* 40+ funny random occurrences to experience!

Special thanks to...
... Molvine & his subscribers, for sharing the idea and supporting development
... amazing beta-testers: 000Magician000, JustFlower & Santanist
... you, for playing the mod! :)

NOTE: Multiplayer is, quite sadly, unsupported at the moment. Feel free to contribute to the mod's GitHub directly via the Home page link!	